[
  {
    "question": "What is the Total area of Nepal According to New political Map realesed in 2020 AD?",
    "options": ["148,519 Km", "147,518", "147234Km", "147516Km"],
    "answer": "147516Km"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
    "options": ["Earth", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Venus"],
    "answer": "Mars"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the present Hpome Minister of Nepal?",
    "options": ["Ramesh Lekhakh", "Rabi Lamichhane", "CK Raut", "Ram Baran Yadav"],
    "answer": "Ramesh Lekhakh"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is known as the smallest planet in solar system?",
    "options": ["Earth", "Mars", "Mercury", "Venus"],
    "answer": "Mercury"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the first president of Nepal?",
    "options": ["Bidya Devi Bhandari", "Dr. Ram Baran Yadav", "B.P koirala", "Bhimsen Thapa"],
    "answer": "Dr. Ram Baran Yadav"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is known as the?",
    "options": ["Earth", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Venus"],
    "answer": "Mars"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the national colour of Nepal?",
    "options": ["Crimson Pink", "Crimson Red", "Crimson Blue", "Crimson Green"],
    "answer": "Crimson Red"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital city of Australia?",
    "options": ["Sydney", "Canberra", "Perth", "Melbourne"],
    "answer": "Canberra"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which planet is known as the Biggest planet in solar system?",
    "options": ["Earth", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Venus"],
    "answer": "Jupiter"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the total area of Nepal according to new political map released in 2020 AD?",
    "options": ["14148Km", "147518Km", "147516Km", "14516Km"],
    "answer": "147516Km"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many district are there in koshi province?",
    "options": ["14", "12", "10", "11"],
    "answer": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many district are there in Nepal?",
    "options": ["6", "74", "75", "77"],
    "answer": "77"
  }
]